curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Do you have a lot of friends?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "How easy is it to read books in English?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Would you like to go back there again?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "What do you do together with your family?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Why is family important to you?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Are you learning a musical instrument at the moment?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "What do you do in your free time?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Has your life changed much in the last year?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Do you have a job right now?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "What book would you take on a long journey?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Is live music popular in your country?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Do you consider this place your home?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Do you like to sing along to your favourite songs?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Do you lead an active life?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Which actor would you like to play you in a film?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Where are you from"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "How often do you go to the cinema?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "What kind of person is it easy to make friends with?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Who are more important to you, friends or family?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "How important is your hometown to you?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Is there anything you dislike about learning English?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "How many people are there in your immediate family?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Where were you born?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Are cinema tickets expensive in your country?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Do you prefer to buy books or borrow them?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "What are the advantages of seeing a film at the cinema?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Where was the last place you visited on holiday?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Do you have a busy social life?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "What job do you think you will be doing in five years?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Who do you get on best with in your family?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Do you have a large extended family?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "How many people live in your hometown?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "How do you listen to music?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "What do you enjoy about learning English?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Who would you most like to be friends with and why?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "What did you want to be when you were a child?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "What skills and qualifications are required for this job?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Do you usually watch films alone or with others?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Are your music tastes varied?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "How will you you use English in future?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "What would you like to change about your lifestyle?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Who is your best friend and why?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Are there good job opportunities in your home country?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Have you given up reading a book recently?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "What is your hometown famous for?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "What kind of tourist destination do you usually prefer?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Has a foreign visitor ever stayed at your home?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "How many books do you have at home?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Who do you live with?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "What kinds of city do you like?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Do you think people in your city will walk more in the future?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "If you can choose, will you move to another city ?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Do most people in your country (still) wear a watch nowadays?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Did you walk more in the past ?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "What do people in your country do during holidays?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "How often do you read?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Do you like going to the cinema?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Do you like perfume?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Do you use email?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Have you ever been to a concert before?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "What do you do when you visit them?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "What's the most common sport in your country?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Can you sense (or feel, or tell) if someone's smile is fake?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Do you like to watch movies? (Why?)"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Do you think young people organize their time in the same way?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Do you often watch a movie (a film)?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Is your voice similar to that of a family members?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Do you like it when it's raining?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Is playing outside good for children?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Is there a good place to look at the sky where you live?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Would you say young people are more patient than older people?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "What kind of pets are common in your country?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "How often do you have a drink of water?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "What's your favorite kind of music?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Did you prefer team sports or individual sports when you were young?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "What kind of places have you visited in your life?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "When you visit new places, what do you like to do?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Do males and females generally use the same kinds of bags?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "What apps do you often use?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "What kinds of apps do you expect in the future?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Do you think your city is clean or not?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Have your sleeping habits changed since you were younger?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Do you prefer visiting your relatives, or your friends?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "How do you organize you time?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Are you ever late for anything?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Do you spend time playing outside or inside ?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "What do you like most about your job?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "What are the most interesting and the difficult part of your job?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Which city have you been to recently?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Do you use perfume?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Would you ever give perfume as a gift?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Do you often watch sports on TV?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Do you like to share things with your friends?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Do you have a favourite movie star?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Do you prefer to write on a computer or to write using a pen?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Would you prefer to live in a place that has the same weather all year, or a place that has four seasons?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Did you sleep more in the past than you do now?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Do you take anything when you visit your relatives?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "How do you feel when other people are impatient?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Do you prefer to drink bottled water or tap water?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Why do you use some social networking apps ?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "How do you like your courses?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "How do you feel in crowded places?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Do you like E-books?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Do you ever read professional books?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "When did you start listening to this type of music?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Have you ever been to a musical performance?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "How do you think parents could encourage their children to share?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Would you say most people in your country know why you have those holidays?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Have you ever seen a movie star in real life?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Do you like handwriting ?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "When do you think children start to have their own ideas?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Should parents follow their children's ideas or should they say “No” to them? Can children say"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "How many hours do you sleep every day (or, every night)?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "What makes a good teacher?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Which major will you change it to?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Do many people live in your neighbourhood?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Which city do you want to go to?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Where do you listen to it?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Do you like sports?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Who do you often spend holiday with?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "When you go out do you most often drink tea, or coffee?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "When you were young, did your parents teach you to share with others?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "What is the perfect holiday for you?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Do you prefer to (or usually) watch a film alone or with others?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Do you like to receive handwritten letters and cards?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Do you often look at the sky? (Why?)"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "In the future, are you planning to learn other languages"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Do you like it?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "How long have you been living there?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "What do you like about the area around where you live?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Where did you play when you were a child?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Are there anything you dont like about your city ?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Do you often (like to) listen to music?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Do you think females are good at maths?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Do you think these holidays are important?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Can you suggest why some people throw their litter on the ground?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Would you move to another city because of the weather?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Did you learn anything about the planets and stars at school?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Do you think old people need more sleep than young people?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Do you often visit your relatives? (Why?)"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "When are you impatient?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "What kind of pets do people like/dislike to have?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "What specific things do you do on your job?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Did you play at your friend's home?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Do you think it is difficult to learn a new sport?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Do you like travelling?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "What is the best season to travel in your country?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Do you prefer to drink tea, or coffee?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "What do you think when your friends borrow your phones"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Do you have a favourite holiday?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Which do you prefer, an information app or a chat app?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "What's the weather like in your city?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Do you feel the climate is changing?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Can you see the moon and stars at night where you live?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "no?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Do you think teachers should be strict?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Do you think people should be patient?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Can you give any examples of work that require patience?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Do you like to smile?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Have you ever had (or, raised) a pet?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Do you like to drink water?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Do you make plans every day?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "What changes would you like to see in this area?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Where do you often walk ?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "What are the most crowded places in your hometown (or where you are living now)?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Is music an important subject at school in your country ?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Do you think maths is important?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Some people think that maths isn't needed in our life. What do you think?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Do you usually wear a watch?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Does your country have many public holidays?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Do you prefer a long holiday or several short ones?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Would you like to be a movie star?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "How do you feel when you see other people throw garbage on the street?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "How often do you smile?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Which languages do you speak ?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Will you change it if you have the chance?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Where are you living at the moment?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "When was the last time you were in a crowded place?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Have you ever learned to play a musical instrument?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Where would you like to travel for a vacation? (Why?)"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Do you like maths?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "How often do you use a calculator?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Have you ever borrowed money from others?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Do you want to develop an app yourself?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "How often do you use email (or, write emails)?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Do you think plastic bags are a serious environmental problem?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Are there four different seasons in your hometown?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "In what ways do you think teachers and parents are different when teaching young people?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Do you prefer to drink hot water or cool (or cold) water?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Do you think you will use more those social networking apps ?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "What's your major?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Is it different from what you had in mind?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "What did you do on the first day of your job?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Do you like the city you are living in now?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "What kind of watch do you wear?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Why do you like tea, coffee?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Is there anything that you would not share with others?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Has your taste in movies changed since you were younger?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Do you prefer to use email or text messaging?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Would you say your handwriting is easy for others to read?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "What do you do when you see rubbish on the street?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "What do you do with the garbage when you are on the street?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Do you know much about the stars and planets?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "When was the last time you visited them? what did you do?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Way to learn languages"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "How often do you begin to learn math?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Which major do you want to choose in college? Why? (if you do not have a major yet)"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Why did you choose that major?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Do you work or are you a student?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Why did you choose that job?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Do you prefer the city or the countryside?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "What kinds of book do you like to read?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "How often do you play sports?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "When was the last time you drank some tea or coffee?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Which is more popular in your country, drinking tea or drinking coffee?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Do people in your country ever give tea as a gift?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Do you like to lend things to others?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Do you think there should be more public holidays?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Do you often use apps on mobile phones?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Do you usually write ?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "What's the biggest difficulty you have when managing time?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Would you like to be a teacher?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Are you patient in your work or study?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Do many people in your country have a pet?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "When does your voice change?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "What work do you do?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Do you think this job has a bright future?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Do you usually read for leisure or for work purposes?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "How much time do you spend listening to music every day?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Are there many celebrity athletes in your country?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Do you prefer traveling alone or in a group?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Are you willing to share your favourite possessions?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "What public holidays do you have in your country?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "What types of films do you like to watch?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Why do some people throw garbage on the street?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Do you do different things in different weather (or different seasons)?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Are you a patient person?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Do you think you will be more patient in the future?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Do you drink much water every day?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Is bottled water very expensive in your country?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Would you say you manage your time well?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Would you recommend that job to others?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Do you have many friends there?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Would you say people with the same interests usually get along with each other when they are in a crowd?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Do you like to listen to live music?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "How do you feel when you listen to this music?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Do you prefer watching or playing sports?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "In which seasons do you prefer to travel?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "How do you feel when people don't return things they borrowed from you?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Do you think it's important to reply to emails immediately (or, quickly) after you receive them?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Do you think a person's handwriting reflects their personality?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Does the weather in your country change often?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Do you think the weather is more important to people who play sports?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Do you prefer to look at the sky in the daytime, or at night?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Do you think it's good to have a nap during the day?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Do you have a favourite teacher?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Do you think you are more patient now than when you were younger?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Do you smile when you are having your picture taken?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "What is the difficulties in learning languages ?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Do you consider living in the countryside in the future?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Do you like crowded places?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Do you prefer to go to crowded places or places that have few people?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Do you like reading?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "When do you listen to music?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "What kinds of music do you like to listen to?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "When people in your country entertain guests do they usually drink tea, or coffee?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Have you ever borrowed books from others?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Do you think it's important to have enough sleep (each day/night)?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "When do people smile to others?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Is your voice different from when you were young?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Do you like listening to yours recordings?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "What are the advantages and disadvantages of social networking apps?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Do you think it is an easy way to make friends through social networking apps?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Are you planning to move to another area to live?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Do you spend much time in the countryside ?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "What was your favourite book or story when you were a child?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "How much traveling have you done?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Do you like bags?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Do you think there will be a car sharing in the future?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Do you prefer a holiday at a beach or other?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "How often do you go to a cinema?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Are any foreign movie stars famous in your country?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Do you think it's important to keep the city clean?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Which season do you like best? /Do you have a favourite type of weather?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Can you explain why some people are not very patient?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Would you say it's important to drink water?"}'
curl --location --request POST 'localhost:8080/create' --header 'Content-Type: application/json' --data-raw '{"answer":"", "question": "Have you ever had an experience of being thirsty, but not having any water to drink?"}'

